mi.edu 2017-03-23

# MUSICIANS INSTITUTE

                                 MUSICIANS INSTITUTE                                                              6752 Hollywood Blvd., Hollywood, CA 90028
                                 COLLEGE OF CONTEMPORARY MUSIC
Musicians Institute Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how Musicians Institute (MI) uses and protects any information that you give MI when you use this website. MI is committed to ensuring that your
privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used
in accordance with this privacy statement. MI may change this policy from time to time by updating this page.You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are
happy with any changes.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
      » Name
      » Contact information including email address
      » Demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
      » Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
      » For the exhaustive list of cookies we collect see the List of cookies we collect section.
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
      » Internal record keeping
        We may use the information to improve our products and services. We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information
        which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided. From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for
        market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.
      » Security
        We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic
        and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
      » How we use cookies
        A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or
        lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your
        needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps
        us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and
        then the data is removed from the system. Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which
        you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.You can choose to
        accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may
        prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
      » Links to other websites
        Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control
        over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites
        are not governed by this privacy statement.You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
      » Whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for
        direct marketing purposes
      » If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at
        registrar@mi.edu
      » We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal
        information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
What is retargeting?
The main goal of retargeting ads (also known as remarketing ads) is to re-engage visitors after they have left the MI site. Dynamic retargeting ads are generated based on
the actual information viewed on the MI site. For example if you have visited mi.edu and viewed a specific department page, you might receive an advertisement containing
copy referring to that department. Rather than showing the same ad to every visitor, software can select the most relevant ad copy based on the user’s activity on the site.
Personalized retargeting systems work via tags on the MI website. This tag embeds a third party cookie on the browser of users visiting the mi.edu site, enabling the advertising
platform to serve up relevant retargeting ads to that user. It is important to note that the cookie itself does not contain any personal identifying information. Instead, retargeting
ads match the right offer to each visitor based on that visitor’s previous activities on the MI site.
How can I opt out from being retargeted?
MI makes removing our tracking cookie easy for any user who chooses to do so. Users that don’t want to see MI’s personalized retargeting ads should visit:
http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the
information held on you please write to 6752 Hollywood Blvd. Hollywood, CA 90028.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly
correct any information found to be incorrect.
                                                                                                                                                               Revised: 05.13.13
      Email    music@mi.edu                              Tel   323.462.1384           Fax   323.462.1575         Toll 1.800.255.7529                             Web    mi.edu
